

Good Morning, how are you today?

Andres Gregorio Puig andres.gregorio 14@gmail.com +34 607 21 80 04

https://nl.linkedin.com/in/andresgpuig

Profile (2)



I amv a UX and UI research designer, with work experience in research institutes and strongly design oriented. I have rediscovered my passion for research through human-centered design projects and its multiple methodologies. My interests reside in exploring new opportunities in multidisciplinar teams, where collaboration is key for success.



Education 🕸



UI/UX Design Bootcamp

Neoland - Barcelona - Sep-Dec 2018 UX research based on Design Thinking and Lean UX methodologies. Interface design, including interacction softwares and prototypying, producing high-fidelity products ready to ship in the market.

Current projects:

https://medium.com/@andresgpuig

MSc Nanomaterials Science

University of Utrecht 2015 - 2017

BSc Chemistry

University of Barcelona 2010 - 2015

Work Experience



R&D Researcher - Philips Lighting, High Tech Campus Eindhoven

March 2017 - August 2017 Improving light efficiency of phosphor rod materials for LED-based devices.

Master thesis - Condensed Matter & Interfaces, Utrecht University

2015 - 2017

Temperature dependence of luminescent properties on lanthanide-doped nanocrystals.

Coordinator in Educational Projects CIC School Barcelona

2012 - 2017

Language

English - Full professional proficiency **Spanish** - Native Catalan - Native

Dutch - Basic user (A2)

Other Skills



Illustration - Digital Illustration

Frame-by-frame Animation

Music - Classic piano (8 years of education)

Bartending – Worked as a bartender

in multiple locations (Utrecht, The Netherlands)

https://medium.com/@andresgpuig https://www.instagram.com/uncertrail/ <

